I need to score better
outside of classic lit...
I can't get a medical excuse for the quiz.
No one gets a medical excuse for a quiz.
Oh, studying around the kotatsu, are we?
We have exams coming up.
Nice! How about I join you—
Go away.
We don't have a place for you, Kyosuke.
Huh?
Just Sota, me, Miyamura, and Mom.
Hey...
Are you treating me worse by the day?
I might just cry.
I swear my wife uses this
language wrong sometimes.
Oh? How so?
I was super depressed...
so my wife cooked a meal to cheer me up.
She sounds like a great wife.
She grabbed my shoulder
and said with a serious face...
Hori Kotatsu
"A-A journey of a thousand miles
begins with fifty to a hundred steps..."
Bathroom...
Ow...
What are you doing?
What time is it?
Hori-san, wait, wait, wait!
Don't get up! Lie back down!
Huh?
Yeowch!
My leg! My leg! My leg! My leg! My leg!
CRAMPED
Your leg?
I mean, someone's leg is locking
my knee and I can't get up!
It's not mine.
*It's hers
Aw, man... I just want to go to the bathroom.
Just do it there.
Don't be unreasonable!
Huh? What time is it?
Around ten or so?
Ouch!
Keep it down, Kyoko.
You're twisting my leg when you move!
That's ridiculous. Right, Miyamura-kun?
Wait, Miyamura-kun? What's wrong?
I need to go to the bathroom...
I know. I'll wake up Sota.
He'll catch cold if he sleeps here.
Sota...
You're wrenching my leg, Miyamura-kun!
Stop moving, Kyosuke!
A cruel world where we all harm each other...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
What now? Should we call for help?
That'd be too embarrassing. We're entangled
like something out of a pervy book.
Right, Miyamura-kun?
Ouch!
You get out, Kyosuke! It's your
fault this is so complicated!
Hori
Dad
Miyamura
What was that? I'd get out if I could.
I can't take this anymore.
I need to go so bad I can't even get up.
You two figure it out.
Don't give up, Miyamura!
Let's review the situation.
We need a plan. Someone must be sacrificed.
Okay, I'll pull as hard as I can.
Please wait.
Kyosuke-san's right leg
is stuck between mine.
Hori-san's legs are also wrapped
pretty tightly around me.
Pulling will cause lots of pain
but ultimately fail.
I see.
So what do we do?
I'll yank as hard as I can,
so you two bear with it!
Hold it right there!
What kind of idiotic idea is that?!
Then answer me this! Does anyone
need the bathroom more than me?
And what about me?! My skirt's flipped,
but I'm not complaining!
That's not the same thing!
No one can even see it!
Don't go back to sleep, Kyosuke!
Disengaged
I shouldn't have drunk so much tea.
Man...
Wait, hang on.
I did it! One of my legs is free!
Really? That's great!
One of mine is free, too!
Kyosuke, wake up!
Huh?
All right, I'm out!
Did Miyamura-kun make it in time?
I'm glad that crisis is over.
I've got it.
Instead of lying down in
three different directions,
Hori
Dad
Miyamura
Hori
we can all do it the same way.
Good thinking.
They all slept in the kotatsu.
When I woke up last time,
it was already dark.
I'll go home at seven today.
That gives us about an hour.
Crap. I might fall asleep.
Oh, don't be silly.
Hey, aren't you Sengoku's boy?
Do you remember me?
You used to come to our house to play.
Y-Yes, you're Kyo-chan's...
Boy, you sure grew a lot.
No wonder, given you're Kyoko's age.
Man, that takes me back
to my high school days...
Listen to me, Kakeru.
The Horis are trouble. The parents
have been since high school.
You have to hold your ground! Let them
lead you by the nose and you're in for it!
In for what?
Trouble with a capital T!
So, Kake... Uh, T-Takeru-kun,
how's your dad doing?
My name's Kakeru!
My dad is doing well, thank you.
Oh? He is, is he?
He's going to do something to my dad!
Excuse me. I was just
on my way to buy an eraser...
Since you're here, why not stop by our place?
It's cold. Come in and warm up.
No, wait... I...
Hey. Hey, old man.
What? I just fell asleep.
When did Sengoku get here? And how?
Around nine. I ran into him
outside and invited him in.
Then while we were talking,
I started getting real sleepy.
Miyamura, it's midnight.
Gotta save... before the dungeon...
Huh?
Right, President...?
Can't forget to save, can you...?
Oh, yeah, and buy some
MP recovery items in town...
Yeah...
Encounter! Encounter!
A g-golem appeared!
Huh? Why are you looking at me?
Calm down, President!
I'll cast a destruction spell!
You calm down first!
Great! The hero's party is here!
You stay out of this!
Wait, what's the president doing here?
I was abducted in my own neighborhood.
His doing, I'll bet.
I haven't had a bath or eaten
dinner, and I took a long nap.
Oh, yeah, wouldn't wanna miss my bath.
Just use ours and quit whining, you two.
Huh? But I can't show him.
There's something you don't want me to see?
Nope, nothing!
Hey, that's right! You waited until late
at night to use the bath on our field trip!
D-Did I?
You wouldn't get in the pool, either.
I was wondering why that was.
Well, y'know, I'm just so scrawny.
If you're scrawny,
I might as well be a skeleton.
Th-Th-That wasn't supposed to be funny!
3 unread messages
Where are you?
I did it again...
This kotatsu's bad news.
Miyamura, wake up—
3 unread messages
Man, he left his phone open.
You've got messages—
Oh, crap. I sent those to Miyamura.
So that's why Chika hasn't shown.
"Where are you? I know it's cold and all,
but I'd like to apologize for the other day."
"Can you come to the park near school?
I'll be waiting there."
"You can say whatever you like. I'll still
love you, even though I don't say it much."
"I know you'll understand—"
"Love you"?!
Miyamura! Hey, Miyamura!
What do you want, Shindo?
Ow!
Huh?
Sting
I feel like someone punched me
in the head as hard as they could.
That can't be, can it? Of course not.
Hori-san, are you asleep?
Oh, you're awake.
Just faking it, huh? It's eight o'clock.
I know that.
Why are you angry?
The cause is a mystery...
It's him
I'm not angry.
Really?
I just said I wasn't.
Hey, lookee here.
We've got mikans, your favorite.
I'll peel one for you.
Wow, she actually got up for that.
Better not laugh, Izumi.
I decided I'd only eat two a day!
So you hate mikans now?
I don't like mikan-flavored things.
Same with yuzu, citron, and grapefruit.
I don't want it!
What? But I just peeled it for you.
Here.
Get it away!
Here. Here, here. Here.
If you don't eat it, I'll kiss you.
And I'll kiss you if you do eat it.
Thank goodness you're not angry anymore.
Is that what he's been up to?
Hey, that message—
Why did he give it to me like that?
Is it habit?
Want a candy?
Is it?!
I won't stand for that.
Here we go again.
That was our elementary camp trip.
I didn't expect to find pictures
like this at Sengoku's house.
We've been friends a long time, after all.
Sengoku, you haven't changed one bit.
Oh? Y-You think so?
Huh? President, what album is that?
What pictures are in it?
O-Oh, it's nothing special.
Just some boring ones—
What's in there, Miyamura? Well?
Miyamura-kun, let's play some games!
We still have a Super Nintendo!
You wanted to play it, remember?!
Christmas with Kyoko-chan
Elementary school graduation, at the front door
Congratulations!
Entering middle school, smiling with friend
It says, "Sengoku, age 12,
screws up cutting his hair."
I wanna see! Pass it here, Miyamura!
No! You're killing me!
Man, this is hilarious.
Give it up, Sengoku!
Kyoko-chan and Kakeru swimming in the kiddie pool
Not a chance!
Lolicon.
N-No!
So, Miyamura, if three is as low as you go,
what's your upper limit?
I don't do less than high school age,
thank you very much.
Does Kyo-chan still get changed
in front of other people?
Do any girls change
She's a third-year.
What? I mean, just the other day, she...
Student Council
I have phys ed first period!
Sengoku, let me borrow
this room for five minutes.
Sure.
I don't have time to go to the changing room.
Kyo-chan.
Doesn't this make you self-conscious?
I'm still in the room.
Huh?
So what? I could still use the toilet
or the bath with you in the room.
Why do you ask?
She doesn't see it as a big deal at all!
I thought it was a bit odd, so I asked
if the same went for Miyamura-kun.
And she said...
I'd never do that!
She seemed angry.
I-I see. Sorry, I guess.
We took baths together all the time as kids.
Well, as kids, sure.
Hang on. When was the last time we did it...?
Huh?
I feel like we did it for an
inappropriately long time...
But I'm afraid to try to remember.
Kindergarten or so?
Oh, yeah. Maybe first grade at the latest.
I need to keep quiet!
Figures.
Crispy
Nori Balls
Lightly salted
Baked, not fried
They have them!
Nori Balls
Lightly salted
Baked, not fried
Crispy
Sota said he likes these,
so I wanted to try them.
Huh.
I'll go check out.
I-I'm so sorry. Thank you.
Koyanagi-san?
What? Y-You're mistaken.
Sengoku...?
Would you happen to be Hori's daughter?
Oh, you're Sengoku-kun's father!
Kakeru-kun is always such a help to us.
Kind of you to say.
You're the president's father?
Hello, I'm Miyamura.
The council president and I have
become good friends.
What a difference! Please don't let
the Hori family corrupt you!
Huh?
Um, I can hear you.
The president's father seems pretty nice.
They're practically identical.
Think he'll look like that in a few years?
By the way, who's Koyanagi-san?
Oh, that's my mom's maiden name.
My parents and Sengoku's father
went to the same high school.
Huh.
Probably goofed off
Two years younger
Always smiling
Probably serious (impression)
I wonder what things were like back then.
Hey, what are your parents like?
My parents?
Hmm, ordinary.
Oh, so just like mine.
Dummy! You still had half left!
You guys stay quiet way too long.
We're not staying quiet.
The conversation just keeps dying.
Isn't that right, Kakeru?
He's terrible at this.
Huh?
That's not true. I was just reminiscing.
Right, Kakeru-kun?
Um, sure.
You can be honest, Kakeru-kun.
There you go, ignoring his opinion.
Get me out of here.
We're back! Gosh, it's cold!
Hey, President! You're here!
Welcome back.
His dad's here, too.
I remember you. Hurry on inside.
Hey, why are you two sitting by me?
You could sit over there.
It's cold by the window.
Now, why are you and your dad here?
Your dad ran into mine
coming home from work,
and he abducted us both.
You're both really good at getting abducted.
The class president's so skinny,
I feel a draft.
I'm sorry.
Miyamura-kun, do you live here?
You walked right in.
Half of the time, I suppose.
He's dating Kyoko.
Aren't they a cute couple?
Is that so?
Well, Kakeru has no time for such things.
Huh?
Kakeru doesn't need a girlfriend.
It would interfere with his studies.
President, what's he talking about?
Are you hiding it from him?
Not hiding, exactly. I just haven't
gotten around to telling him.
I was waiting for the right time,
and I invited Remi over for Christmas...
I want it to be in my room!
But I ended up going to her place instead.
I was surrounded by insects.
So it's remained a secret ever since.
Huh?
The "So it's a secret, is it?" face
President, are you cold?
The way you're shaking is concerning.
Don't tell him.
Huh? Tell your dad what?
What's up?
Tell me what?
Just tell him that you've been
dating someone for quite a while.
Just tell him that you've been dating someone for quite a while. You'll feel so much better.
You'll feel so much better.
A loose cannon.
Say, president,
how is Ayasaki-san today?
Oh, I'm sorry! You're keeping her
a secret, right? That just slipped out.
And an oblivious time bomb.
The oblivious time bomb is the real danger...
Namely, you!
Huh? I'm a person!
Kakeru-kun probably has someone he's into.
Isn't it unreasonable to say he can't date?
This could work!
Maybe this will settle things!
Shut up. Enough of that.
Stay out of our family affairs.
Your whole way of thinking
is outdated. Get with it.
Don't boss me around. I'm older than you!
You bring me here on my personal time
and think you can lecture me?
When you forgot your lunch,
I gave you some bread from the store!
Yeah, about that!
That bread cost 80 yen,
but you asked me for 100!
They're not even talking about
the same thing any more.
How ungrateful! I can't believe you!
Kyoko, don't be like this when you grow up!
It almost seems...
Did you hear that, Kakeru?
This is fraud, plain and simple!
Instead of adults, they're fighting like...
High schoolers.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
Walking through what looks like a rain puddle
can get you soaked up to your knees.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
You already said that!
Although, compared to the idiot who arrived
at school after all the exams were over...
That was only because
someone stole my front wheel!
Then walk instead!
This is embarrassing. I wish they'd shut up.
YAMMER YAMMER
Yeah? It's always like this here.
You two are such good friends.
Yup! We're best friends, right, Sengoku?
Shut up! Best friends, my ass!
I'll never forgive
what you did at graduation!
Just as I was giving my
speech as council president...
Speech
Achoo!
You had that sneeze planned, didn't you?!
That sneeze... came from
the student body rep.
We didn't have a student body rep!
Let's go back to talking
about Sengoku's girlfriend.
SHOCK
No! Feel free to keep reminiscing!
Don't try to laugh it off!
It seems that the Sengokus...
are still at the mercy of the Horis.
Listen, Kakeru. You do not
need a girlfriend right now.
Especially not one like Hori's daughter.
There's no way I can tell him now!
Imports are stuff that comes into Japan...
I hope I can score at least 40 on this.
Can I get that high? I'm not so sure.
Did you study for math?
I gave up.
You gave up at the beginning
of the school year.
Try picking it back up instead.
You're eating so many.
Your nails will turn orange.
I'm not eating that many.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Here.
Me eating won't do anything
about your fingers.
I know.
This is like...
feeding an animal! I'll give him another.
I cleaned your finger.
Drip
It's not clean.
Hori-san, I'll skip everything
except classic lit.
Huh?!
Next time
page.5 Iura